(Sheldon:)Leonard could
frequent sushi bars,
(Sheldon:)salad bars, oyster bars,
(Sheldon:)the Apple Genius Bar...
What are you doing?
(Leonard(exiting the apartment):)Keep going. I'm listening.
(Amy:)That was rude.
(Sheldon:)He does it all the time.
(Sheldon:)He's a cornucopia
of social awkwardness.
(Sheldon:)Cornucopia.
(Amy:)What a mellifluous word.
(Sheldon:)Let's make that our word
of the day.
(Amy:)Agreed. And we'll use
mellifluous tomorrow.
(Sheldon:)Well, I have to void my bladder.
(Sheldon:)It was nice spending this time
with you.
(Amy:)Wait.
(Amy:)I have a request.
(Sheldon:)Yes?
(Amy:)I'd like you to meet my mother.
(Sheldon:)I see.
(Sheldon:)Can I get back to you on that?
(Amy:)Certainly. Good night.
(Amy:)Good night.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, Leonard, Leonard,
Leonard, Leonard,
(Sheldon:)Leonard, Leonard,
Leonard, Leonard, Leonard,
(Sheldon:)Leonard, Leonard, Leonard,
Leonard, Leonard,
(Sheldon:)Leonard, Leonard,
(Sheldon:)Leonard, Leonard...
(Leonard:)Yeah, what?
(Sheldon:)Amy Farrah Fowler has asked me
to meet her mother.